Contact

90678851 (Mobile) praphan90@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/praphan-huat-chai-3896319a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Engineering
Microsoft Office
Communication

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Malay (Professional Working)
Chinese (Professional Working)
Thai (Elementary)

Praphan Huat Chai

Resident Engineer at Surbana Jurong Private Limited Singapore

Summary

Experienced Resident Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the architecture & planning industry. Skilled in AutoCAD, Engineering, Communication, Adobe Illustrator, and Microsoft Office. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Engineering - BE focused in Civil Engineering from Universiti Selangor (UNISEL), formerly known as Universiti Industri Selangor.

Experience

Surbana Jurong Private Limited Resident Engineer August 2020 - Present (2 years 4 months) Singapore, Singapore

I am currently working at Surbana Jurong Consultants Pte Ltd as a Resident Engineer.

Metrocon Pte Ltd Project Manager July 2019 - February 2020 (8 months) Singapore, Singapore

Pintary Foundations Pte Ltd Senior Project Engineer August 2018 - July 2019 (1 year) Singapore, Singapore

CIVIL TECH PTE. LTD. Assistant Project Manager July 2017 - June 2018 (1 year) Malaysia & Singapore

CS Bored Piles System Pte Ltd Project Engineer January 2015 - April 2017 (2 years 4 months) Singapore, Singapore

Ho Lee Construction Pte Ltd Project Engineer July 2014 - January 2015 (7 months) Singapore

Education

Universiti Selangor (UNISEL), formerly known as Universiti Industri Selangor

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Civil Engineering · (May 2010 - May 2014)